Phone: (360) 927-7744

Email: leo.g.stewart@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/leogstewart Website: leo-gs.github.io/

Advanced stage PhD candidate with extensive experience building data infrastructure, analysis, and visualization pipelines. Broad research competencies developed through PhD work, including social media and APIs, demographic methods, machine learning, and large-scale parallel computing. Eager to apply the critical thinking skills I have developed during my PhD.

Data Infrastructure	Data Analysis	Mobile Development
R (4 yrs)	Data visualization (4 yrs)	Kotlin (<1 yr)
Python (3 yrs)	Scholarly research (5 yrs)	Java (2 yrs)
SQL (4 yrs)	Social network analysis (3 yrs)	Native Android dev. (2 yrs)
_	_	
REST APIs	Shiny apps	Jetpack Compose
Data scraping	RMarkdown	Gradle
PostgreSQL	LaTeX	Unit testing

EDUCATION

University of Washington Seattle, Washington	Ph.D. Candidate, Information Science	2018 – present
	M.S., Information Science	2021
	B.S., Human Centered Design & Engineering B.S., Computer Science	2017 2017
	Graduated with Interdisciplinary Honors	

	B.S., Computer Science Graduated with Interdisciplinary Honors	2017
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
University of Washington Seattle, Washington	Teaching Assistant Supervised by Ted Neward	Fall 2023
	NIH T32 program in Data Science and Demography Fellow Supervised by Sara Curran	2021 - 2023
	Graduate Research/Teaching Assistant Supervised by Emma Spiro, Anna Lauren Hoffmann, Ott Toomet, Jaime Snyder	2018 - 2021
Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation Seattle, Washington	Data Analyst Supervised by Daniel Dicker	2017 – 2018
	Research Intern Supervised by Amber Sligar	Summer 2017
Motorola Solutions Seattle, Washington	Mobile Software Developer Intern Supervised by Leslie Lamprecht	Summer 2016
	Mobile Software Developer Intern Supervised by Leslie Lamprecht	Summer 2015
Qualcomm, Inc.	Engineering Intern	Summer 2014

Qualcomm, Inc.San Diego, California

Engineering Intern Supervised by Kenny Fok